ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pants Negotiations, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Basic Data for the Separate Trousers Industry Negotiations, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Basic Data - Shirts, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Some Long-Run Trends in the Shirt Industry, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Negotiation Meeting Shirts - A Substantial Wage Increase, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Expiration Dates - Cotton Garments, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Data for the Negotiations, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Summary of Data in Connection with the Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Data for the Single Pants Negotiations, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Companies Controlling Major United States Men's Clothing Manufacturers Under Contract with the ACWA, 1968-1974 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Controlling Companies in the Cotton Garment and Allied Industries, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Cuttings of Men's Separate Dress & Sport Trousers and Men's Jeans-Cut Casual Slacks, By Month, 1973-1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Cuttings of Men's and Boys' Jeans-Cut Casuals Slacks, 1970-1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Cuttings of Men's and Boys' Separate dress and Sport Trousers & Jeans-Cut Casual Slacks Combined, 1970-1975 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Average Weekly Earnings in the Men's & Boys' Suit & Coat Industry, 1967-1976 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Average Weekly Manhours for the Men's + Boys' Suit + Coat Industry, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Potofsky Minimum Wage Testimony, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- JSP Statement in Opposition to the Proposed Equal Rights Amendment to the Constitution, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- JSP Statement at Opening of Negotiations - Men's & Boys' Clothing Industry, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Statement of J.S.P. - ACTWU, AFL-CIO On Amendments to the Fair-Labor Standards Acts, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Statement on The Apparel and Textile Industries to the AFL-CIO General Board, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Special Reports on Apparel Industry, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Major Male Apparel Manufacturing Companies, Other than Tailored Clothing, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Retail Sales in Men's and Boys' Stores/ The Outlook for the Men's and Boys' Apparel Industries, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- ACWA Statement on 4 day, 4Hour Week by VM, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- International Activities of 28 Major Companies Operating in the Men's & Boys' Apparel Industries, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Profits + Sales (Major Apparel Companies), 1971 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Overseas Licensees of U.S. Male Apparel Companies, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Companies of Productivity, Cost of Living and Hourly Wage Increases, 1968-1972 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Some Long-Run Trends in the Men's Clothing Industry, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Statement of the ACWA on the need for a $3.00 Federal Minimum Wage, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Major United States Men's Clothing Manufacturers Under Contract with the ACWA, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Major Manufacturers of Cotton Garments, Outerwear, and Single Pants (ACWA), 1967 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Net Profits of Net Sales - As a percentage of Tangible Net Worth in Men's & Boys' Shirt, Underwear, and Nightwear Industry, 1935-1970 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Proposals Relating to the Fund to Protect Employees of Outside Shops Making Canvas Coat Fronts who are Displace by Fusing, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- A Re-Evaluation of State Protective Legislation for Women Workers, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Vera Miller Misc. Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Letter to Editor of N.Y. Post - re. Training, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Japanese Shipments of Men's & Boys' Apparel to the U.S., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Material for Conference on Impact of Intern. Trade of Investment, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- A Brief Appraisal of the Tariff Commission Report on Textiles and Apparel, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Obits, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Newspaper Clippings
- OSHA, 1977-1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Women Workers Joyce Miller, 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Elections Contracts Strikes (Oct.), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- NLRM Elections Strikes Contracts, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Elections Contracts Strikes, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Elections Contracts Strikes (March - May), 1980 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Election Contracts Strikes (April-June), 1980 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- October, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- November, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- JP Stevens, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Amalgamated Institutions (Bank etc.), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- April-May, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Misc./ Local Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Misc./Local/Scene - (Jan0Aug), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Misc./Local/Scene (Aug-Oct), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Misc./Local/Scene (Oct-Nov), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens (July 1981-Nov-1982), 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Women, Child-Care, Social Services (Nov 1982-June 1983), 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- CLUW Joyce Miller (Jan-Nov), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- O.S.H.A. - Brown Lung Cotton Dust (Jan-Jun), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- O.S.H.A. - Brown Lung (May-Jul), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Women, Child Care- Abuse Unemployment - Day Care Centers, Rehab. Programs (Feb-May), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Hanes - May, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Politics/National Scene (Jan-Nov), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- O.S.H.A. - Health Hazards (Jan-Nov), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Footwear/Shoe Division (Jan-April), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Footwear/Shoe Division (May-June), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Women/Social Services (May-), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Hanes (July-), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Hanes, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- CLUW - Joyce Miller Social Services (Feb-Mar), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens (Jan-May), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Biographies of Important ACTWU People (Feb-Se), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Misc. - Local Scene (Mar-Apr), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Misc. - Local Scene (Apr-May), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Misc. - Local Scene (May-Jul), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens (May-Jul), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Amalgamated Institutions, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Politics, National Scene (May-Jul), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Legislation. Politics - National Scene (Jan-Apr), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Biographies - Important People, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Elections - Contracts - Strikes (Jun-Jul), 1980 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Loose Newspaper Clippings in Box. (Box 38, Folder 24)
- 13. Companies Hanes, Stevens, etc. (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- 12. Misc. Local Scenes (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- 2. Imports - Buy American Quotas (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- News clippings, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- 10. Social Services REHAB (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- 8. ACTWU Institutions - Includes Convention (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Cannon (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- 7. Labor (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- 6. Votes, Talks, Walkouts Strikes (June-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- CLUW, Women, J. Miller (Sent to JM) (Nov-Jan), 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- 11. mf/JS/SH (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- 5. Obits (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- 4. Biographies (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- 3. OSHA (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- 1. Elections, NLRB, contracts, National Political Scene (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- mf/JS/SH, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- 9. CLUW, Women, J. Miller (Jun-Dec), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- ACTWU Institutions Burrelle's (July-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Women, CLUW, Joyce Miller Burrelle's (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Social Service Programs, Rehab Burrelle's (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Burrelle's - Elections, NLRB Contracts, National Political Scene (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Burrelle's - Imports "China" "Buy American" (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Burrelle's - OSHA (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Burrelle's - Biographies (Feb-June), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Burrelle's - Obits (Feb-June), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Burrelle's - Votes, talks, walkouts, strikes (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Burrelle's - CLUW, Women, Joyce, Miller (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Burrelle's - Labor (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Burrelle's - Social Service/REHAB (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Burrelle's - ACTWU Institutions (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Burrelle's - MHF/JS/SH (Feb-Jun), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Burrelle's - Misc./Local Scene (Feb-), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Burrelle's - Hanes/J.P. Stevens (Feb-), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Burrelle's - Elections, NLRB, Contracts (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Burrelle's - News clippings, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Burrelle's - Misc. (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Burrelle's - MHF/JS (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- February - March, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- December-January, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Imports/China "Buy American" (Dec-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Biographies (Dec-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- October-November, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Burrelle's - OBITS (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Burrelle's - OSHA (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Burrelle's - Votes, Talks, Walkouts, Strikes, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Labor (Nov-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Burrelle's - HANES (Jul-Feb), 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- (April-May), 1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- June, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- July, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- August, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- September, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Cannon #2, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Imports - Buy American (Feb- Apr), 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Cannon #1 (Jan-Dec), 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Other (Aug-Jun), 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Misc., Local Scenes (Oct-Jun), 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Imports - Buy American Quotas (Jan-Aug), 1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- August, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Other, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Talks, Strikes (Jun-Mar), 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Imports, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Votes, Talks Walkouts, Strikes (Nov-Jul), 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Obits, 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Biographies, 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- OSHA, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Elections, NLRB, Contracts, National Political scenes, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Companies. Hanes, Stevens, etc, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Social Services, Rehab, 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Institutions, 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Labor, 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- ACWA Clipping Index File (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Burrelle Clips, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Burrelle Clips, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Burrelle Clips, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Burrelle Clips, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Burrelle Clips, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Burrelle Clips, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Burrelle Clips, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Burrelle Clips, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Burrelle Clips - Elections/Strikes/Contracts NLRB, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Burrelle Clips - ACTWU People, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Burrelle Clips - ACTWU Institutions, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Burrelle Clips - Elections/Contracts/Strikes, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Burrelle Clips - Misc., 1981 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Burrelle Clips - Research, 1984-1987 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Burrelle Clips - File, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Burrelle Clips - Dominion Textiles, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Burrelle Clips - Other, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Burrelle Clips - Voting, Contracts, Strikes, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Burrelle Clips, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Burrelle Clips, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Burrelle Clips, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Burrelle Clips - Strikes; Elections; Settlements; Co. news, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Burrelle Clips - (Mar-Apr), 1979 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Burrelle Clips, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Burrelle Clips, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Burrelle Clips - Joyce Miller, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Burrelle Clips, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Burrelle Clips - J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Burrelle Clips - J.P. Stevens, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Burrelle Clips - Joyce Miller CLUW, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Burrelle Clips, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Burrelle Clips - Biography - Obits, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Burrelle Clips - General Labor, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Burrelle Clips - ACTWU Institutions, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Burrelle Clips - Social, Legal, Financial Services, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Burrelle Clips - Strikes, Organizing, Bargaining, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Burrelle Clips - Politics, Legislation, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Burrelle Clips - Imports, Trade, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Burrelle Clips - OSHA, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Burrelle Clips - Misc., 1986 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Burrelle Clips - CLUW, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jul-Sep), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Oct-Dec), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jan-Mar), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Apr-Jun), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jul-Dec), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jan-Mar), 1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Apr-Jun), 1979 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jul-Sep) - I, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jul-Sep) - II, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Oct-Dec), 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jan-Mar), 1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Apr-Jun), 1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Burrelle's Clips - J. P. Stevens (Jul-Sep), 1980 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Tom Thompson, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Tom Thompson, 1981-1983 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Tom Thompson (Jacks assistant), 1978-1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Legal - (Arthur Goldberg), 1973-1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Jack Sheinkman (Apr-Dec), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Jack Sheinkman (Jan-Mar), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Murray H. Finley, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Murray H. Finley, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Murray H. Finley, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Murray H. Finley, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- International Trade Affairs (Gundersheim), 1977-1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Organizing (Swaity - Lewis), 1976-1982 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Vera Miller - Vice President, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Vera Miller - Vice President, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Vera Miller - Vice President, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Vera Miller - Vice President, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Vera Miller - Vice President, 1977-1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Vera Miller - (Pay Board Advisory Committee), 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Vera Miller - (Trustee), 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Vera Miller - Special Activities/Bibliography (Personal-Committees-Resume'), 1947 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Inventory List of Numbered Files, 1970-1978 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- No. 503 - Cuttings; Employment, Hours, and Earnings; And the outlook for the Male Apparel Industries, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- No. 504 - Shirt and Blouse Imports, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- No. 505 - Study to Determine the Factors related to Successful Men's Tailored Manufacturing in NYC, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- No. 506 - Proposed Language for Farah Cost-of-Living Adjustment Clause, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- No. 507 - Supplemental Agreements, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- No. 508 - Import Data Sources, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- No. 509 - Information Reported by ACWA Affiliates on the Apparel Plant Information Survey Questionnaires, First Quarter, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- No. 535 - Puerto Rico Minimum Wage Committee Hearings, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- No. 536 - Cost-of-Living Adjustment, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- No. 537 - Wages of Production Workers, Cost of Materials, Value added by Manufacture, and Value of Industry Shipments, in the Men's and Boys' Suit and Coat Industry, 1958-1974 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- No. 538 - Projections of Total Employment in the Textile and Apparel Industries, 1976-1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- No. 539 - Materials Prepared for the Meetings with the Zensen Domei Delegation/ Men's and Boys' Clothing Industries, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- No. 544 - Directory of Manufacturers of Men's, Boys', and Children's Apparel Operating Under ACTWU Contract, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- No. 546 - ACTWU Joint Boards and Locals (Box 51, Folder 19)
- No. 552 - Statement to Amend the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- No. 556 - Statement on H.R. 50, The Full Employment and Balanced Growth Act of 1977, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- No. 558 - Impact of the ACTWU Boycott on the Financial Condition of J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- No. 559 - Statement on H.R. 50 the full Employment. Balance Growth Act of 1977 (By J. Sheinkman), 1978 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- No. 561 - Table A. Employment and Payrolls, in the Apparel Industry, By State, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- No. 586 - Convention - Statement on Economic Policy, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- No. 587 - Local 169 Negotiations and other 169 materials, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- No. 591 - Convention - Statement on Foreign Policy, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- No. 592 - CETA - Philip Ross, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- CETA Training of Sewing Machine Operators (April 16), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Provisions in Laws & Collective Agreements Concerning Redundancies Resulting from Lay Offs and Closures (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Active Workers Covered by the Retirement (Jan 1-Jul 23), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Tenth Paid Holidays (Nov 19), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- T-2 Median First-Year Wage Increases, 1971-1978 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Carter's Wage/Price Standards and ACTWU Bargaining (Dec 13), 1978 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- Carter's Wage/Price Standards and ACTWU Bargaining #2 (Jan 5), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 35)
- Carter's Wage/Price Standards and ACTWU Bargaining #3 (Feb 14), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 36)
- Wage Guidelines (Jan 10), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 37)
- Adjustment of Minimum Wages and Wage Progressions (Aug 13), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Survey of Number of Organizers and Length of Campaigns reported for Representation Elections & Agreements for Newly Organized Male Apparel and Related Establishments, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 39)
- Survey of Number of Organizers Representation Elections & Agreement & Length of Campaigns (Nov 6), 1978 (Box 51, Folder 40)
- Puerto Rico (Mittens & Gloves) 141-A Industry Committee Hearings, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 41)
- Leather 141-B Industry Committee Hearings, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Men's Boys' Clothing Industry Committee Hearings No. 142, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Puerto Rico (Clothing) Minimum Wage Committee Hearings, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 44)
- Materials for the Meeting in Canada, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 45)
- British - North American Committee Paper by Charles Carterr, Endemic Unemployment + Outline of a Problem, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Government Procurement of Apparel, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 47)
- Companies awarded Government Contracts for Apparel with Shipping points in Puerto Rico, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 48)
- Material for Conference on the Impact of International Trade + Investment on Employment, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 49)
- Statement by the ACTWU & the ILGWU on the Proposed Field Memorandum on Training Sewing Machine Operators Under CETA (Aug 8), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Joint Response by ACTWU and the ILGWU on the Revised Proposed Field Memorandum on Training SMO Under CETA (Jan 11), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 51)
- D & L - Workers in Plants (Jul 27), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 52)
- D & L Workers in Plants Revised (Aug 20), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 53)
- Employment Data for Companies which were members of the National Bargaining Committee Rep. By D & L (Sep 1), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 54)
- Establishment Closings + Company Liquidations of Clothing, Pants, Outer-wear + Related Companies, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 55)
- Statement of Sidney Bykofsky, ACTWU on The Plant Closings and Community Assistance Bill N.Y., N.Y. (Dec 12), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 56)
- Effect of Imports on Textile/Apparel Employment, Selected Areas, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 57)
- Imports of Tailored Clothing, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 58)
- Local 169 Negotiations, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 59)
- Convention - Statement on Economic Policy (Aug 17), 1978 (Box 51, Folder 60)
- Comments of Robert M. Dale (Aug 2), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 61)
- New Income Tax Credits for Employers for Certain Newly Hired Workers (U.S.Dept. of Labor) (Apr 20), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 62)
- ACTWU Affiliates Having Contracts with Robert Hall Clothes, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 63)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott (Feb 22), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 64)
- ACTWU Boycott on the Financial Condition of J. P. Stevens & Co., (Feb 17), 1978 (Box 51, Folder 65)
- Folder #1 (Laundry/Cleaners/Dryers), 1938-1947 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Folder #2, 1937-1948 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Folder #3 (Laundry Industry), 1946-1947 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Folder #4 (Laundry Industry), 1939-1947 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Folder #5 (Laundry Industry), 1917-1942 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Folder #6 (Laundry Industry), 1943-1951 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Folder #7 (Laundry Industry), 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Folder #8 (Laundry Industry), 1946-1947 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Folder #9 (Laundry Industry), 1946-1949 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Folder #23 - J.P. Stevens & Company - Company correspondence to Scott Hoyman re: first contract negotiation, 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Folder #22 - J.P. Stevens & Company - Draft first contract, and correspondence (S. Hoyman), 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Folder #25 - J.P. Stevens & Company - Pension materials re: first contract negotiations (Scott Hoyman files etc), 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Folder #26 - J.P. Stevens & Company - First Contract Negotiations (Cafeteria Issue) Scott Hoyman File, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Folder #24 - J.P. Stevens & Company - Scott Hoyman (Chief ACTWU negotiator notes of first contract negotiations), 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Folder #19 (Textile/Apparel Division), 1978-1981 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Folder #10 (Laundry Industry), 1940-1955 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Folder #11 (Laundry Industry), 1937-1946 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Folder #12 (Laundry Industry), 1937-1947 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Folder #13 (Laundry Industry), 1937-1946 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Folder #14 (Laundry Industry), 1945-1961 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Folder #15 (Laundry Industry) - Operating Cost Percentages, 1949-1961 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Folder #16, 1919-1965 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Folder #17 (Laundry Industry) - Occupational Evaluations, 1946-1960 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Folder #18 (Laundry Industry), 1956-1961 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Folder #19, 1945-1950 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Folder #20 (Laundry Industry), 1944-1951 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Folder #24 (Laundry Industry), 1943-1951 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Folder #22 (Laundry Industry), 1950-1953 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Folder #23 (Laundry Industry) - Laundry Drivers, 1944-1951 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Folder #24 (Laundry Industry), 1944-1951 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Folder #25 (Laundry Industry) - Medical Care, 1944-1957 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Folder #1 (Laundry Industry) - Laundry Wages, NY, 1943-1962 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Folder #2 (Laundry Industry) - Diaper Service Drivers/Minimum Wage, 1944-1965 (Box 54, Folder 8)